export const _flashcards = [
  // To mutate the original array
  {
    key: 1,
    question: 'To add element to the original array (end)',
    answer: '.push',
  },
  {
    key: 2,
    question: 'To add element to the original array (start)',
    answer: '.unshift',
  },
  {
    key: 3,
    question: 'To remove element from the original array (end)',
    answer: '.pop',
  },
  {
    key: 4,
    question: 'To remove element from the original array (start)',
    answer: '.shift',
  },
  {
    key: 5,
    question: 'To remove element from the original array (any)',
    answer: '.splice',
  },
  {
    key: 6,
    question: 'To reverse the original array',
    answer: '.reverse',
  },
  {
    key: 7,
    question: 'To sort the original array',
    answer: '.sort',
  },
  {
    key: 8,
    question:
      'To change all elements within a range of indices in an array to a static value',
    answer: '.fill',
  },
  // A new array
  {
    key: 9,
    question: 'To compute a new array from original (loop)',
    answer: '.map',
  },
  {
    key: 10,
    question: 'To filter the array using condition',
    answer: '.filter',
  },
  {
    key: 11,
    question: 'To get a portion of the original',
    answer: '.slice',
  },
  {
    key: 12,
    question: 'To merge 2 or more arrays',
    answer: '.concat',
  },
  {
    key: 13,
    question: 'To get a new array with all sub-arrays flattened',
    answer: '.flat',
  },
  {
    key: 14,
    question:
      'To get a new array formed by applying a callback function to each element',
    answer: '.flatMap',
  },
  // An array index
  {
    key: 15,
    question: 'To get the index based on value',
    answer: '.indexOf',
  },
  {
    key: 16,
    question: 'To get the index based on a test condition',
    answer: '.findIndex',
  },
  // An array element
  {
    key: 17,
    question: 'To get an element based on a test condition',
    answer: '.find',
  },
  // Know if array includes
  {
    key: 18,
    question: 'To know if an array contains a value',
    answer: '.includes',
  },
  {
    key: 19,
    question: 'To test whether at least one element passes a test condition',
    answer: '.some',
  },
  {
    key: 20,
    question: 'To test whether all elements pas a test condition',
    answer: '.every',
  },
  // A new string
  {
    key: 21,
    question: 'To get a new string based on a seperator string',
    answer: '.join',
  },
  // To transform to value
  {
    key: 22,
    question: 'To transform to a value based on an accumulator',
    answer: '.reduce',
  },
  // To just loop array
  {
    key: 23,
    question: 'To simply loop the array based on a callback',
    answer: '.forEach',
  },
  {
    key: 24,
    question: 'Monkey loves you',
    answer: 'Monkey needs a hug',
  },
];
